Website **Dan Chanivet** https://www.chanivetdan.tech **Email** chanivetdan@hotmail.com

Argentina > Buenos Aires

Gender: Male, Age: 36 years

Phone

+549-11-2482-1510

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dan-

chanivet-574084b2/

Github

https://www.github.com/flan02

Skills

Javascript & Typescript

Git & Github

Linux Ubuntu & Debian

MongoDB Atlas

React

Redux & Hooks

Zustand

React Query & SWR

Nodejs & express.js

APIREST

GraphQL

TailwindCSS & SASS

Framer Motion

Particlesis

Nextjs

Vercel CI/CD

tRCP

Prisma Studio & Zod

Figma

Postman

Python

Cloudinary 3.0 project. April 2023 - Present (2024)

Profile

Fullstack Web Developer with over 4+ years of experience in programming through different companies in IT. I use to develop the MERNT stack creating beautiful websites and experiences for users in real time.

I have strong backend skills creating servers, middlewares, routes, APIs with nodejs and expressis. When it comes to persist user's data I usually work with nosql database MongoDB Atlas Cloud environment.

working remotely with customers from EE.UU. keeping conversations for a long time in English. As a highly motivated, professional and organized person, I enjoy a fast-paced and collaborative team environments.

My native tongue is Spanish but I'm fluent in English too. I have experience

I'm feel ready to take the next big step in my career and I'm looking for a remotely job in a foreing company that allow me grow up as a programmer and being a better human.

Education

High School degree: Maria Mazzarello Institute. Argentina. 2004-2006

English Certificate B2 Cambridge Institute. Argentina 2001-2005

React Course Argentina Programa 4.0. Government of the city of Buenos Aires certificated course. 2020-2021

Javascript ES6+ Essencial I & II. Cisco Networking Academy (online). 2019-2020

React Frontend Developer Course. National Technology University (UTN) Argentina. 2021

Database Admin Manager. MongoDB University (online). 2022

Employment History

FrontEnd developer with javascript in Club Argentino Castelar. August 2018 - November 2019

React Developer in Federacion de Basquet Argentina. May 2020 - December 2021.

Nextjs Developer in Picnic App for stores and delivery food. January 2022 - December 2022

I managed my own site writted with php core, mysql, javascipt with domain in https://www.2kceltics.xyz. December 2020 - Present (2024)

FrontEnd dev with typescript, react, framermotion, figma developing apps for web